Dylan Tremmel

Web/Database Developer

Personal Info

Email

ctremmel22@gmail.com

Phone

862-202-4858

Skills

Unix, Linux, Windows

Java, Python, PhP

HTML, CSS, JS

Git

SQL, MySQL

Microsoft Office/Google Suite

Bash Scripting

Vulnerability Classification

Malware Analysis

Languages

English





Self-motivated ethical hacker with an exceptional grasp of the command-line across Linux/Unix and Windows systems. Extensive experience in UI/UX design/development. Savvy with crafting SQL queries and Google Sheets formulas to maximize effectiveness of data retrieval, aggregation, and alteration.

My official website (features my projects): https://dylans0gt.github.io/officialwebsite/index.html

Work History

2020-07

IT Specialist | Sales Associate | Social Media Manager

- present

Brookdale Pet Center, Bloomfield, NJ

Troubleshoot, test, and fix printers, card machines, routers, and computers. Install new desktop hardware.

Monitor our email inbox for any suspicious-looking, potentially phishing emails, and educate my coworkers on phishing to ensure no company information gets in the wrong hands.

Manage our store's social media presence.

Research all pet products we sell and craft talking points to sell them to customers.

Create and post social media content to boost traffic to our store's website and generate more attention to our store overall.

Utilize Google Sheets formulas to automate the repetitive steps of data entry. Utilize Google Forms to collect and analyze customer feedback on new products, sales, and services.

2018-09 - 2020-06

Leadership Experience | FIRST Robotics Club Vice President

Bloomfield High School, Bloomfield, NJ

Helped complete the challenge of building a 120-pound robot in 6 weeks for 3 consecutive years.

Handled the wiring and cables of the electrical components of the robot. Repaired glitches in the robot code and optimized the code by changing multiple if-else statements to switch statements and/or while loops.

Produced and uploaded videos of our team's endeavors and posted them on our social media accounts.

Education

2016-09

N/A, Diploma

- 2020-06

Bloomfield High School, Bloomfield, NJ

2020-08 - present Computer Science & Cyber Security, In Progress

Drew University, Madison, NJ

Awards

2019-03 Xerox Creativity Award (FIRST Robotics)

2020-06 National Honor Society Award

2016-06 **Bengal Pride Award**

Certificates

2022-01 CO

COMPTIA Security+